Finding aid to the Classes of 1941-1950 records CA.MS.01016
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1949 Records, 1945-2004; 7 boxes (2.9 linear feet); 3.708 linear feet (9 containers)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 5)
  - Commencement-Theater Program, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 6)
  - Commencement-Last Chapel, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1945-1946 (Box 2166, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1945-1949 (Box 2166, Folder 9)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 12)
  - Junior Ushers, 1948 (Box 2166, Folder 13)
  - May Day, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1958-2002 (Box 2166, Folder 15)
  - Occupations, 1949 (Box 2166, Folder 16)
  - Officers, 1945; 1999 (Box 2166, Folder 17)
  - Organization, 1949-1957 (Box 2166, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 2166, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 2166, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 2166, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 2166.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1984 (Box 2166.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2166.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2166.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 2004 (Box 2166.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 2166.1, Folder 6)
  - Smith Centennial Newsletter, 1975 (Box 2166.1, Folder 7)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1947 (Box 2166.1, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Committee, 1947 (Box 2166.1, Folder 9)
  - Step Sing, 1949 (Box 2166.1, Folder 10)
  - Class Supper, 1949 (Box 2166.1, Folder 11)
  - Individuals A-L (Box 2167)
  - Individuals M-Z (Box 2168)
  - Elizabeth Banks course notes (Box 2168.1)
  - Mary-Clare Milligan (Box 2168.2)
  - Lois Green course notes (Box 2169)
  - Carolyn French (Box 2170.1)
  - Mary Lou Burditt scrapbook (Box 2170.2)
- Class of 1950 Records, 1946-2002; 2.5 linear feet (9 containers)
  The Class of 1950 was the seventy-second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1950 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1950, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 1)
  - Commencement-Dramatics, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 4)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 5)
  - Commencement-Speaker, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Dance, 1947 (Box 2171, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1946-1947 (Box 2171, Folder 8)
  - General, 1947; 1968 (Box 2171, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1946-1950 (Box 2171, Folder 10)
  - Hoop Rolling, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1949 (Box 2171, Folder 14)
  - Junior Ushers, 1949 (Box 2171, Folder 15)
  - Class Letters, 1960-1976 (Box 2171, Folder 16)
  - Class Newsletter, 1996-2002 (Box 2171, Folder 17)
  - Officers, 1947 (Box 2171, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 2171, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 2171, Folder 20)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 2171, Folder 21)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 2171, Folder 22)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 2171, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 2171, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 2171, Folder 25)
  - Reunions-45th, 1995 (Box 2171, Folder 26)
    (See individual box)
  - Senior Prom, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 27)
  - Senior Song, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 28)
  - Sophomore Carnival, 1948 (Box 2171, Folder 29)
  - Step Sings, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 30)
  - Class Supper, 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 31)
  - 45th Reunion-Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunion Questionnaires, 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Questionnaires, 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunion Questionnaire-note on restrictions, 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunion Questionnaire-Script with Statistics and Comments, 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 5)
  - 50th Reunion Book, 2000 (Box 2171.2, Folder 1)
  - Reunion individuals A-Z (Box 2171.3)
  - Individuals A-Z (Box 2172)
  - Elinor Kuhn: Southern Mountain Workshop (Box 2173)
  - Dorothy Jean Lobrano correspondence, photos (Box 2173.1)
  - Barbara Moyer (Conklin) correspondence with Marshall Schalk (Box 2174)
  - Roxanne Wheldon Junior Year Abroad photographs (Box 2174.1)